Hi! Check out my first ZK Game: Snarks and Starks United.
The UI is still a work in progress.
This is a ZK Extrasensory Perception game.
You and your friends can have fun playing against each other.
Here's how it works:
John has loaded the app and will create an account.
The onboarding is easy and clean for users (no private keys or seed phrases).
John just needs to press a button and set his nickname to create (and, in the background, deploy) his Starknet account.
Then, to create a game, we copy the account address and fund the wallet.
Now we set the bet amount for this game.
And choose our secret number.
Finally, we approve our entry fee to register the game and place our bet on Starknet (hashed commitment).
Now, let's tell our friend Mike to play with us.
For onboarding, he must create his new account.
And fund his new account to join a game using John's Game ID.
Now Mike sets his own secret number and joins our game.
Now John will try to guess Mike's secret number.
Using his paranormal powers, he believes it is 11.
Now Mike receives the guess and checks whether the number is correct.
John failed, so now Mike will try to guess John's secret number.
Mike believes that John's secret number is 55.
Now John receives the number, creates the proof, and sends it to the blockchain for verification.
Bad luck for John!! Mike has stronger ESP powers.
Mike wins and claims his reward!...:)